<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Stumbling Blog</title>
    <link>https://blog.ianmkim.com/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Stumbling Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <copyright>© Ian Kim 2022</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 13 Mar 2022 15:30:07 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.ianmkim.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Fayerabend: The Last Savior of Science</title>
      <link>https://blog.ianmkim.com/posts/fayerabend_savior_of_science/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Mar 2022 15:30:07 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ianmkim.com/posts/fayerabend_savior_of_science/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Critics of Feyerabend all follow patterns of behavior undeniably similar to each other. No matter which way they turn, a simple extension of their logic regresses to the beginning of Feyerabend’s argument. In no other criticism is this more apparent than in Chalmers’ “middle lane” counterargument. When drawn to its conclusions, we see that Chalmers puts himself in a double bind. If he wishes to end anarchism, Chalmers must make dogmatic claims which stand at the beginning of Feyerabend’s normative arguments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seize the Means of Production (The Right Way)</title>
      <link>https://blog.ianmkim.com/posts/seize_the_means_of_production/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Nov 2021 15:54:52 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ianmkim.com/posts/seize_the_means_of_production/</guid>
      <description>Introduction The foundations of libertarian ideology are intuitive and require little justification: Individuals own themselves, they own their labor, and they own justly acquired property. These seem like excellent foundations for a political ideology. Yet, it doesn’t seem to account for the apparent immorality of mass wealth inequality caused by a hypothetical Artificial General Intelligence agent (AGI). To explore the libertarian response, let’s consider a future in which Jeff Bezos creates an AGI, which now runs the global conglomerate monopoly, formally known as “Amazon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Duty to Drive</title>
      <link>https://blog.ianmkim.com/posts/duty_to_drive/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Oct 2021 15:47:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ianmkim.com/posts/duty_to_drive/</guid>
      <description>The Duty to Drive Given the promise of safer-than-human levels of proficiency, mandating self-driving cars seem like an attractive proposition at face value. The following argument will prove that such a mandate would be a severe violation of man’s right to an agentive life which outweighs its benefits. More importantly, the very acceptance of unsupervised self-driving cars represents a mass abdication of moral responsibility. This abdication will cheapen moral agency and set a precedent for other technologies that our moral intuitions reject.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reviving AI through Heidegger</title>
      <link>https://blog.ianmkim.com/posts/reviving_ai_through_heidegger/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 16:36:59 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ianmkim.com/posts/reviving_ai_through_heidegger/</guid>
      <description>Introduction When the term Artificial Intelligence was coined at the Dartmouth Workshop in 1956, the organizers defined AI beyond narrow automata theory or simply solving problems more generally; the explicit intention was to re-create human cognition (McCarthy, 1). Unfortunately, we have considerably strayed from those goals. Today&amp;rsquo;s thinking machines operate well under narrow contexts but fail to accomplish elementary human tasks. Moreover, even in those areas where they work well, they require tremendous resources, and the pace of progress is grinding to a halt (Dellinger, 2).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
